Your call is being...
...connected...
...by SewerCom.
Reach out and touch the sewers.
Look, Morris, it's Leela calling.
Hi, Mom, hi, Dad.
Ready for your big trip to the surface?
We're excited, honey,
but we don't want to embarrass you.
I mean, your mother and I
are basically monsters.
Dad, relax.
You are being so mutant.
I found this adorable little bag
to wear over my head.
And it was on sale.
No one's wearing anything
adorable over their head.
Now, listen.
I could never ever
be ashamed of my parents.
I'll see you this weekend.
Hey, guess who
I just got off the videophone with.
No.
My parents!
They're coming up
from the sewers for a visit Sunday.
Are you off your rocket?
Your parents are mutants.
It's illegal for them to come above ground
'cause they're inferior genetic scum.
Uh, present company excluded, of course.
I'm getting them a special one-day
surface permit from CitiHall.
Ooh, while you're there,
could you pick me up a license to kill?
Sure. Bare hands or weapon?
Uh, what does piano wire count as?
Good news, anyone.
The Swedish robot from Pi-kea
is here with the supercollider I ordered.
Enjoy your affordable Swedish crap.
Let's see what tools we'll need.
Uh-huh.
All right, we're all set.
Nothing like the rustic wholesomeness
of working with one's own hands.
Ah, there. Finished.
And only six missing pieces.
Those Swedes sure know
how to put in almost everything you need.
Man, I'm sore all over.
I feel like I just went
10 rounds with mighty Thor.
I feel like I was mauled by Jesus.
I've got just the thing.
Genuine miracle cream I bought
from a traveling salesman.
"Come one, come all," he said.
"Step right up."
"This sounds too good
to be true," I thought.
He said I looked like a smart young man.
"So, is it a deal?" I inquired.
Two hours later, he was gone
with 60 of my dollars.
But I had the miracle cream.
Bad news, nobody.
The supercollider super exploded.
I need you to take it back
and exchange it for a wobbly CD rack
and some of those rancid meatballs.
Excuse me. Hi. Do you have a minute?
I live in Jersey City
and my car broke down
and I need to get back
'cause my aunt's real sick
and she needs this medicine,
but I need money for the bus.
So I'm mugging you.
Hand over your wallets.
I don't believe that story for a second.
It doesn't matter, I'm mugging you.
There's no bus to Jersey City.
Give me your wallets now
or my robot will shoot.
Don't make me hurt you.
I'm too scared to find my pocket.
Here, I'll just take off my pants
and give you those.
Hey, I don't like what I'm seeing.
Give it to 'em, Andrew!
Give it to 'em again, Andrew!
Ah!
What the...
Laser-proof shirts, huh?
I'll show you.
Huh? Hey. Quit it.
Hi-ya!
Foiled.
And after years of planning.
You're out of the gang.
How did we manage to survive?
What gave us those strange powers?
Maybe we're all wearing magic rings
but they're invisible rings
so we don't even realize it.
Also, you can't feel the rings.
Oh, Fry!
Shut up and look at this.
"May cause superpowers in humans."
Wow.
A superpowers drug
you can just rub into your skin?
You'd think it'd be something
you have to freebase.
Let's see, which powers do we have?
"Super strength"?
Ah!
Hi-ya!
- Yup.
- Uh-huh.
"Lickety-speed"?
- Check.
- Yes, sir.
"Ability to command
the loyalty of sea creatures"?
Hey, Zoidberg, get in here.
Screw you!
- Ain't got that.
- Nope.
Wow, superpowers.
I'll be able to pack my day
with twice as many humdrum activities.
Leela, I think you're missing
the big picture.
When you were a kid,
what was your biggest fantasy?
To have parents.
Whatever.
The correct answer is to be a superhero.
We have superpowers, and we're Americans.
This is our chance.
Hmm.
I have been looking for
a way to serve the community
that incorporates my violence.
Let's do it.
You'll barely regret this.
Hey, a friend of mine said
he mugged you today
and you had superpowers.
It's true, thanks
to this funky-fresh cream.
Now me and Leela are forming
an awesome crime-fighting duo.
Wow, crime fighting. Cool.
And you say you're a duo?
Yeah, duos are good.
Of course, sometimes
they're a little shorthanded.
See, ya.
With two humans, you'd think there'd be
a robot in there to balance things out.
But whatever.
I have these three costumes you could use,
but I guess I'll just throw one away.
We'd love to have you on the team, Bender,
but aren't you more on
the supply side of crime?
Plus, the cream
won't give you superpowers.
You're a robot.
So? I'm already super strong.
And my arms do this.
Also, I got this going.
Listen up, New New York!
There's a new group of superheroes in town
and we're...
Quiet! It's 4:00 a.m.
and I just fell asleep
for the first time in 30 years!
Sorry!
A new era of justice has begun.
What?
Attention,
all crooks,lowlifes and lawbreakers.
Do yourselves a favor
and crawlback into your filthy tenements,
you human cockroaches,
or get your ugly face punched
to custard by...
The New Justice Team!
Captain Yesterday!
Clobberella!
And Super King, the best one of the three!
Wow!
Go, go, go, New Justice Team
Go, team, go, team, team, team, team
Who's the newest justice team?
The New Justice Team
Captain Yesterday is fast
Also he is from the past
Not just fast but from the past
Captain Yesterday
Super King has all the powers
Of a king plus all the powers
Of Superman, also he's a robot
Ain't it cool? Super King, you rule
Clobberella beats you up
Who does she beat up? You!
Clobberella!
Citizens, never fear
Crazy do-good freaks are here
Until they run out of steam
Miracle Cream, Miracle Cream
Gives the power to the team
Its effects wear off for sure
So they just slop on some more
The New Justice Team!
Ta-da!
Captain Yesterday,
I find your skintight high-waters
incredibly sexy.
Let's get together sometime.
Sure. I'm listed in the phone book.
So once I reveal my real name to you,
along with my home address
and a copy of my birth certificate...
Are you crazy?
We have to keep
our secret identities secret.
From everybody?
Especially from everybody.
Give several reasons why.
For one, superheroes cause a lot
of collateral damage
and we don't want to get our butts sued.
Or do we?
No, I guess not.
Also, if our identities get out,
every crook in the city will be after us
or, God forbid, our loved ones.
Super King has no need for loved ones.
How you doing, kid?
There you go.
Two one-day mutant surface passes.
Thank you, Mayor Poopenmeyer.
Mayor here. What's that?
A horrible crime in the works?
Ruthless villain?
Citizens in danger?
That's fantastic news!
Because I get to summon
The New Justice Team!
Oh!
Shh.
Huh... They're usually here by now.
Well, so long. Keep in touch.
Wait, stay and meet the superheroes.
There's three of you and three of them,
so it'll be perfect.
Is this clown on?
Where are those daring crime-stoppers?
Oh, I completely forgot!
I left my apartment on fire.
As for me, I'm late for my LSATs.
And I can't take life anymore!
Clobberella! Captain Yesterday! My liege!
You're just in time.
We've received a tip
that the Museum of Natural History
will be robbed tomorrow
at exactly 9:00 a.m.
The target...
The priceless Quantum Gemerald.
Who's the perp?
A dangerous villain
known as the Zookeeper,
who commits crimes
aided by a pack of highly trained animals.
Pack of highly. Got it.
His crew includes a badger
with a troubled past
and nothing left to lose,
an elephant who never forgets to kill,
and a seldom-used crab
named Lucky, aka "Citizen Snips."
You can count on us, Mr. Mayor.
Justice away!
Hold the elevator!
We're in here, too.
Uh, Leela, how are you
going to meet your folks tomorrow?
We've already scheduled the Zookeeper
for a 9:00 a.m. foiling at the museum.
Not a problem.
I've cleverly arranged
to meet my parents right there
at the same museum at 10:00.
Nine, 10, a big fat hen.
The name's Bender.
I can't believe the Zookeeper
is this late for his own heist.
It's just rude.
Total hell! It's 10:00!
I'm supposed to meet my parents
and I'm still in my secret costume.
There they are!
How could Leela not be here?
Do you think she forgot?
Relax. I'm sure she's just ashamed of us.
Yo, freakjobs.
Hit the nearest manhole, pronto-like.
But we have passes
that allow us to be up here,
from the mayor himself.
I don't know. I never heard of no mayor.
The Zookeeper!
Sorry I'm late. Long story.
Now, everybody hit the deck!
I'm cutting the entire line
and stealing the exhibit.
You're not stealing anything.
Nobody hit the deck!
Ah, the superheroes...
Or should I say, "super zeroes?"
That was uncalled for.
Animals, attack.
Please do not feed the animals.
You're going down, my friend!
Down under!
A man boxing a kangaroo
is a peculiar spectacle,
but a kangaroo boxing a robot?
Now I'm afraid you've lost me.
Citizen Snips!
Nice job, Fingers.
I'm scared and confused.
I think we've wandered into
an off-Broadway play.
No, there are way too many people here.
Later, if anyone asks
when I got away, tell them right now.
Forget it, Zookeeper.
You're going into captivity.
Fool!
A quip about putting me behind bars
would have been far more delicious.
Here, catch.
No, Fry, you can't fall fast enough!
I got it, I got it.
I don't got it!
You saved the Gemerald!
Yet the Zookeeper escaped,
thus proving that the deadliest
animal of all is the Zookeeper.
You can get off me anytime.
Oh, no.
My parents are leaving.
I've got to go change back
into street Leela.
There they are.
Thank you, mysterious heroes.
The value of the Gemerald
you saved is slightly greater
than the cost of the damage
you caused to this museum.
A net gain for our great city.
It's good that Leela doesn't love us.
She'll be less sad when we die.
Mom, Dad?
I showed up,
and I got the audio tour
for "Treasures of Liberace's Tomb."
Sweetie, it's okay.
You don't have
to apologize for standing us up
on the only visit
to the surface we'll ever have.
I want to tell you why
I didn't show up, but I can't.
Just please believe me
that it was a very good reason.
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
Leela, you could never disappoint us.
We're so proud of everything that you are.
And we always will be.
Because you're our baby girl.
Oh...
I can't take it.
Mom, Dad...
I'm Clobberella!
Galloping gators!
You're a superhero?
Well, that's wonderful.
But did you have to make
the costume so revealing?
Look at me, proud dad of a superhero.
We should print up T-shirts.
And F-shirts for our friends
with two arms on the same side.
No, listen. It's very important
that you never ever tell anyone.
Under any circumstance.
What if I've had a few?
Dad? You drink?
No, not even then.
All right. My sucker is sealed.
In fact, I shouldn't even
be wearing this around here.
It was brisk.
I dressed in layers.
That's my girl.
So, uh, anyway, my daughter's Clobberella.
Leela is Clobberella?
You're pulling me.
Shh! Keep it under your sock.
It's a big secret.
That's why I'm only telling you two.
Oh, my God.
That guy's daughter is Clobberella.
But don't tell anyone.
Gotcha!
Greeting, superheroes.
Remember me?
I don't remember much, buddy,
and you're no looker.
Uh, Professor, isn't it time for your nap?
Yes, damn it!
Zookeeper, how did you know
our real identities?
Let's just say a little bird told me.
Leela told her parents.
Leela's parents blabbed...
Leela? Is the person
that parrot is mimicking
telling the truth by proxy?
Yes.
My parents were so hurt,
I couldn't help it.
But I distinctly told them
not to tell anyone.
We are not amused.
And here's something you may
or may not find interesting.
Mom! Dad!
Leela, please forgive us.
Especially your father,
who's the one who told!
Thank you very much, Morris.
Are you all right? Has he hurt you?
No, but my allergies are going nuts.
Oh, God!
Every couch and table
has animal fur all over it.
He lets them climb on everything.
All right, Zookeeper, what do you want?
Why, the Quantum Gemerald, of course.
You must steal it for me by midnight
or your parents will be devoured
by piranhas that I have,
shall we say,
persuaded to walk on dry land.
Save us, Leela!
I mean, if you don't have
anything better to do.
We're out of options.
We have to steal the Gemerald.
But should superheroes commit a crime,
even to save lives?
I need moral guidance.
- Bender?
- Hmm...
The thought of stealing anything
fills Super King with disgust.
But if it must be so,
than let a museum heist be pulled!
Oh, no. Our superpower cream
is out of itself.
Check inside the cap.
There might be a caked-in gold mine.
El zilcho.
I'm afraid we're boned.
El Zilcho...
Hey, is it too late
to change my superhero name?
Just be cool.
Nobody knows
we're superpowerly challenged.
Man, this costume is so damn heavy.
Hey, Captain Yesterday.
Can I, like, whale on you with
this two-by-four and it doesn't hurt you?
Ow!
That didn't hurt.
Hi, superheroes. Everything okay?
Big "O", little "K," my friend.
Just checking if everything's all right.
It's okay, all right.
Okay, then.
Grab it!
Yo, the superheroes have turned evil.
Most uncool.
Get 'em!
Stay back!
Or we'll beat the tar out of you,
using superpowers!
So, this is your lair?
Of course not.
You think I'd show you my lair?
My lair's a million times nicer than this.
Okay, take it easy.
Well, here's your lousy Gemerald.
Hawk, fetch.
That seemed unnecessary.
Our transaction is complete.
Come, Solomon, to the lair.
Mom, Dad.
Oh, I'm so sorry I got you
kidnapped by a crazy madman
who tried to feed you to piranhas.
We're just happy to be involved
in your life.
No, no. It's my fault
for telling you I was a superhero.
- That's true.
- I just couldn't stand
to have you think I was ashamed of you.
That's sweet, honey.
But it's natural for children
to be a little ashamed of their parents.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just like it's natural
for parents to be a little disappointed
in their children.
Not that we are.
But you could call a little more often.
Okay.
And would it kill you
to use some mouthwash?
Hey, Fry, we still got our costumes on.
Want to steal some more stuff?
I guess.
As long as you think it's right.
Superheroes away!
Go, go, go, New Justice Team
Fighting justice is their quest
Super King, Clobberella and all the rest
Here's to you, New Justice Team
Do the things that make a team
Help each other do some things
Winners don't use straws
The New Justice Team!